A Guide to the Office of University Relations, General Correspondence File of Bevin Alexander, Director of Information Services, 1961-1965
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Office of University Relations, General Correspondence File of Bevin Alexander, Director of Information Services 1961-1965
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-4/2/1.651
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1977 April 2.
Organization
Series I: General Files, 1953-1963 Boxes 1-2
Series II: General Files, 1962-1964 Boxes 3-5
Series III: General Files, 1963-1965 Box 6
Contents List
- Series I: General Files, 1953-1963
  - Academic Yr. Institute 1958 (Box 1)
  - Admission 1958 (Box 1)
  - Alumni News Correspondence 1961-1962 (Box 1)
  - AMERAD Corporation 1962 (Box 1)
  - American College Public Relations Association--correspondence 1962 (Box 1)
  - Architectural Forum Magazine 1962 (Box 1)
  - Associated Press 1962 (Box 1)
  - Baltimore Sun 1962 (Box 1)
  - Benton and Bowles, Inc.--correspondence re: Benson and Hedges advertisement 1962 (Box 1)
  - Bolivian Students 1961 (Box 1)
  - Bristol Herald Courier1961 (Box 1)
  - Bruns, Mrs. Jean--correspondence 1962 (Box 1)
  - Bureau of Public Administration--correspondence 1961-1962 (Box 1)
  - Cavalier Daily 1953-1961 (Box 1)
  - Charlottesville 200th Anniversary Commission 1962 (Box 1)
  - College Quiz Bowl 1962 (Box 1)
  - Colleges and Universities--correspondence 1961-1962 (Box 1)
  - Commonwealth Magazine--correspondence 1961-1962 (Box 1)
  - Current 1961-1962 (Box 1)
  - Danville-- The Bee; The Register1961 (Box 1)
  - Daily Progress(Charlottesville Daily Progress) 1961-1962 (Box 1)
  - Engineering, School of 1961 (Box 1)
  - Extension and General Studies, Division of 1961 (Box 1)
  - General Correspondence (5 folders) 1960-1961 (Box 1)
  - George Mason College 1961 (Box 1)
  - Information Requests 1961-1962 (Box 1)
  - Lord Kilmer 1962 (Box 1)
  - Legislative Apportionment--correspondence 1961-1962 (Box 1)
  - Library of Congress--correspondence 1962 (Box 1)
  - Lynchburg-- The News and Daily Advance1961 (Box 1)
  - Magazines--Correspondence 1961-1962 (Box 1)
  - Medicine, School of 1961 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous 1961-1962 (Box 1)
  - Movies and Films--correspondence 1962 (Box 1)
  - NBC--National Broadcasting Company 1962 (Box 2)
  - National Observer--Correspondence 1962 (Box 2)
  - Newport News-- The Daily Press; The Times Herald1961 (Box 2)
  - Newspapers--small weeklies and out-of-state papers 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Norfolk-- Ledger-Dispatch; Virginian-Pilot1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Photographs (requests for) 1961-1964 (Box 2)
  - "Please Be Informed" 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Printing Correspondence 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Publicity Calendars--Automobile Mutual Insurance 1961 (Box 2)
  - Reynolds, Herbert B. 1961 (Box 2)
  - Radio Stations 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Requests for Miscellaneous Information 1961 (Box 2)
  - Richmond News Leader 1962 (Box 2)
  - Richmond Times-Dispatch 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Roanoke Times and World News 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Rugby Club--correspondence 1962 (Box 2)
  - Rural Virginia 1962 (Box 2)
  - Seward Forest 1961 (Box 2)
  - Smithsonian Institution--correspondence 1962 (Box 2)
  - Southern Regional Education Board--correspondence 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Sports Information Office--correspondence 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Streeter, R. L. 1962 (Box 2)
  - Summer Session--Correspondence 1962 (Box 2)
  - Staunton-- The Leader; The News Leader1962 (Box 2)
  - Sweet Briar College--correspondence 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Transcontinental Gas Pipeline Corporation 1962 (Box 2)
  - Tulane University--correspondence 1962 (Box 2)
  - TV Stations 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - United Press International (UPI) 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - University Center in Virginia--correspondence 1962 (Box 2)
  - Virginia, Commonwealth of 1962 (Box 2)
  - Virginia Bankers Association 1962 (Box 2)
  - Virginia State Library--correspondence 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - VIMC 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts 1962 (Box 2)
  - Virginia Press Association 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Virginia Press Services 1963 (Box 2)
  - Virginia State Bar--correspondence 1962 (Box 2)
  - Voice of America--correspondence 1962 (Box 2)
  - Voice of America 1962 (Box 2)
  - Washington Post; Washington Star 1959-1962 (Box 2)
  - Waynesboro News-Virginian 1962 (Box 2)
  - WINA 1961-1962 (Box 2)
- Series II: General Files, 1962-1964
  - Advertisement--correspondence 1962-1963 (Box 3)
  - Alumni News--correspondence 1962-1963 (Box 3)
  - American College Public Relations Association--correspondence 1962-1964 (Box 3)
  - Associated Press 1962 (Box 3)
  - Baltimore Sun(folder empty) n.d. (Box 3)
  - Bristol Herald-Courier1963 (Box 3)
  - Bruns, Mrs. Jean--correspondence 1962-1963 (Box 3)
  - Bureau of Public Administration--correspondence (folder empty) n.d. (Box 3)
  - Cavalier Daily 1962-1963 (Box 3)
  - Chamber of Commerce 1963-1964 (Box 3)
  - Charlottesville Daily Progress1963 (Box 3)
  - Clinch Valley College 1962 (Box 3)
  - College Directory 1964 (Box 3)
  - Colleges and Universities 1961-1964 (Box 3)
  - Collegiate Digest 1962 (Box 3)
  - Colonial Williamsburg 1964 (Box 3)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System (CBS) 1962 (Box 3)
  - Commonwealth Magazine 1962-1964 (Box 3)
  - Corks and Curls 1963-1964 (Box 3)
  - Current Miscellaneous 1962-1963 (Box 3)
  - Daily Progress(Charlottesville Daily Progress) 1963 (Box 3)
  - Danville-- The Bee; The Register1963 (Box 3)
  - Editors, Inc. 1962 (Box 3)
  - Faulkner First Novel Award 1964 (Box 3)
  - Florida State University 1964 (Box 3)
  - Garrett and Massie 1963 (Box 3)
  - General Studies, School of (folder empty) n.d. (Box 3)
  - George Mason College 1963 (Box 3)
  - Gonser and Gerber (see also: Woodrow Wilson Foundation) 1964 (Box 3)
  - Hootenanny 1963 (Box 4)
  - "House Organs"--correspondence 1963 (Box 4)
  - Information Requests (2 folders) 1962-1964 (Box 4)
  - Law Weekly 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Library of Congress (folder empty) n.d. (Box 4)
  - Life Insurance Company of Virginia 1964 (Box 4)
  - Lynchburg-- The News and Daily Advance1963 (Box 4)
  - Magazines 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - Mary Washington College 1962-1963 (Box 4)
  - "Meet the Professor"--Association for Higher Education 1962 (Box 4)
  - Motion Pictures/Film--Producers 1962 (Box 4)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA)--correspondence 1963 (Box 4)
  - National Broadcasting Company--correspondence (folder empty) n.d. (Box 4)
  - National Observer 1963 (Box 4)
  - Newport News-- The Daily Press; The Times Heraldn.d. (Box 4)
  - New York Times 1964 (Box 4)
  - Newspaper 1962-1964 (Box 4)
  - Norfolk-- Ledger-Dispatch; Virginian-Pilot1962-1964 (Box 4)
  - Oak Ridge Institute of Nuclear Studies--correspondence 1962 (Box 5)
  - Oak Ridge Institute of Nuclear Studies--Public Relations Seminar 1963 (Box 5)
  - Photographs (requests for) 1962-1964 (Box 5)
  - "Please Be Informed" 1963 (Box 5)
  - Plume and Sword 1962 (Box 5)
  - Printing--correspondence 1963 (Box 5)
  - Professional Journals 1962 (Box 5)
  - Publications 1963 (Box 5)
  - Radio Recording Center 1964 (Box 5)
  - Reader's Digest Magazine 1962-1964 (Box 5)
  - Recording for the Blind 1959-1964 (Box 5)
  - Registrar's Office 1963 (Box 5)
  - Richmond Times Dispatch and News Leader1962-1964 (Box 5)
  - Roanoke Times and World News 1962-1964 (Box 5)
  - Rugby Club 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - Rural Virginia 1962 (Box 5)
  - Saturday Review--correspondence 1963 (Box 5)
  - Scientific American 1964 (Box 5)
  - Southern Regional Education Board--correspondence 1963-1964 (Box 5)
  - Sports Correspondence 1962 (Box 5)
  - Staunton Leader 1962 (Box 5)
  - Supreme Rubber Stamps 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - Sweet Briar College 1964 (Box 5)
  - Tidewater Heart Association 1964 (Box 5)
  - Tour Correspondence 1963 (Box 5)
  - "Transgas" 1964 (Box 5)
  - TV Guide 1964 (Box 5)
  - TV Stations 1963-1964 (Box 5)
  - Union Theological Seminary 1963 (Box 5)
  - University of Florida 1964 (Box 5)
  - University of Maryland 1964 (Box 5)
  - United Press International (UPI) 1962-1964 (Box 5)
  - United States Information Agency 1962-1964 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Cavalcade 1964 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Civil War Commission 1964 (Box 5)
  - Virgnia Manufacturers Association 1964 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts 1963 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute 1963 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Press Association 1962-1964 (Box 5)
  - Virginia State Library 1962 (Box 5)
  - Washington Post and Star1962-1964 (Box 5)
  - Waynesboro News-Virginian 1962 (Box 5)
- Series III: General Files, 1963-1965
  - Advertisement 1963-1965 (Box 6)
  - Alumni News 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Associated Press 1965 (Box 6)
  - Chamber of Commerce 1965 (Box 6)
  - Colleges and Universities 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Colonial Williamsburg 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Corks and Curls 1965 (Box 6)
  - Current Miscellaneous 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Information Requests 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Daily Progress(Charlottesville) 1964 (Box 6)
  - Danville Bee and Register 1964 (Box 6)
  - Fourth of July Celebration Committee 1965 (Box 6)
  - Garden Club of Virginia 1963-1965 (Box 6)
  - Law Weekly 1965 (Box 6)
  - Lynchburg News and Daily Advance 1964 (Box 6)
  - Magazines 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - NBC 1965 (Box 6)
  - Newspapers 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Norfolk Ledger Star and Pilot 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Oakridge Institute of Nuclear Studies 1965 (Box 6)
  - Photos Requested 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Printing Communication 1964 (Box 6)
  - Public Schools 1965 (Box 6)
  - Radio Stations 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Radio and Recording Center 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Richmond Times Dispatch and News Leader 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Roanoke Times and World News 1964 (Box 6)
  - Sperry Piedmont Company 1965 (Box 6)
  - TV Stations 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - United States Information Agency 1965-1966 (Box 6)
  - University Switchboard 1964 (Box 6)
  - Virginia Civil War Commission 1964 (Box 6)
  - VPI 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Virginia Press Association 1964-1965 (Box 6)
  - Washington Post and Star1965 (Box 6)
  - William Byrd Press 1964-1965 (Box 6)